1
00:00:26,902 --> 00:00:27,402
Ta-da!

2
00:00:31,073 --> 00:00:32,165
Ta-da!

3
00:00:32,282 --> 00:00:33,750
Ta-da! Ta...
Ta-da!

4
00:00:36,119 --> 00:00:37,120
Ta-da!

5
00:00:37,621 --> 00:00:38,622
Ta-da!

6
00:02:01,663 --> 00:02:02,710
Huh?

7
00:03:14,945 --> 00:03:18,495
SILAS: Three weeks, and we're
still no closer to cracking this.

8
00:03:19,116 --> 00:03:21,494
Right, bring him in!

9
00:03:21,660 --> 00:03:22,912
Yes, sir.

10
00:03:46,810 --> 00:03:49,154
This is the best party ever!

11
00:04:03,952 --> 00:04:05,204
Yeah!

12
00:04:08,290 --> 00:04:09,963
Ha!

13
00:04:17,382 --> 00:04:20,431
Oh, no!
A dragon is approaching!

14
00:04:25,849 --> 00:04:30,025
Fear not, for here come the
gallant knights to save us.

15
00:04:30,103 --> 00:04:31,195
KIDS: Yay!

16
00:04:47,913 --> 00:04:50,666
No, no, no. What do you
mean she's not coming?

17
00:04:50,791 --> 00:04:53,590
I have a backyard full
of these little girls

18
00:04:53,752 --> 00:04:57,802
who are counting on a visit
from a fairy princess.

19
00:04:57,881 --> 00:05:00,725
Hurts! Stop it!

20
00:05:04,387 --> 00:05:08,642
Listen! I don't want a refund,
I want the fairy princess,

21
00:05:08,809 --> 00:05:11,107
Please, please,
I'm begging you.

22
00:05:11,269 --> 00:05:13,613
You know what? I hope that
you can sleep at night,

23
00:05:13,772 --> 00:05:16,116
you crusher of
little girls' dreams!

24
00:05:16,358 --> 00:05:17,359
AGNES: Ooh, ooh!

25
00:05:17,442 --> 00:05:18,819
When's the fairy
princess coming?

26
00:05:19,861 --> 00:05:21,534
Any minute now!

27
00:05:21,655 --> 00:05:23,578
Yay!

28
00:05:24,115 --> 00:05:25,241
Stall them!

29
00:05:29,538 --> 00:05:30,585
KIDS: Ooh!

30
00:05:40,340 --> 00:05:43,093
Whoa! Whoa, okay!
Okay, all right.

31
00:05:43,260 --> 00:05:44,807
That's enough of
the magic show.

32
00:05:44,928 --> 00:05:45,929
MINIONSI Aw!

33
00:05:48,098 --> 00:05:50,192
Wait, did you hear that?

34
00:05:50,350 --> 00:05:53,980
It sounded like the twinkling
sounds of magical fairy dust.

35
00:05:54,104 --> 00:05:56,527
It's the fairy
princess! She's coming!

36
00:05:56,606 --> 00:05:58,700
Look!

37
00:06:07,617 --> 00:06:09,585
Huh? om

38
00:06:12,789 --> 00:06:14,917
Ow!

39
00:06:16,585 --> 00:06:18,462
KID: Ow.

40
00:06:25,886 --> 00:06:29,936
It is I, Gruzinkerbell,

41
00:06:30,056 --> 00:06:34,436
the most magical
fairy princess of all!

42
00:06:34,561 --> 00:06:38,611
And I am here to
wish Princess Agnes

43
00:06:38,773 --> 00:06:40,992
a very happy birthday!

44
00:06:41,109 --> 00:06:42,986
How come you're so fat?

45
00:06:43,653 --> 00:06:45,371
Because

46
00:06:45,488 --> 00:06:48,082
my house is made of candy,

47
00:06:48,241 --> 00:06:52,087
and sometimes I eat
instead of facing my problems!

48
00:06:52,287 --> 00:06:54,665
How come you have...

49
00:06:54,789 --> 00:06:56,507
Okay, time for cake.

50
00:06:56,666 --> 00:06:57,792
ALL: Yay!

51
00:07:01,212 --> 00:07:04,637
Thank you, Gruzinkerbelll You're
the best fairy princess ever!

52
00:07:04,758 --> 00:07:08,058
You are welcome, little girl!

53
00:07:09,679 --> 00:07:14,185
I know it's really you, Gru. I'm
just pretending for the other kids.

54
00:07:18,438 --> 00:07:21,817
Hey there, Gru. Mr. Life of the Party!

55
00:07:21,983 --> 00:07:23,451
Hello, Jillian.

56
00:07:23,568 --> 00:07:26,697
So, I'm gonna go
out on a limb here,

57
00:07:26,863 --> 00:07:32,836
but my friend Natalie is
recently single, and... Oop.

58
00:07:32,911 --> 00:07:35,710
No, no, no, get off the limb right now.
No limb.

59
00:07:35,872 --> 00:07:38,170
Come on, she's a riot!

60
00:07:38,333 --> 00:07:41,303
She sings karaoke,
she has a lot of free time,

61
00:07:41,461 --> 00:07:44,055
looks aren't that
important to her...

62
00:07:44,214 --> 00:07:48,219
No, Jills, that is not happening.
Seriously, I'm fine.

63
00:07:48,385 --> 00:07:50,763
Okay, fine, forget Natalie.
How about my cousin Linda?

64
00:07:50,845 --> 00:07:51,937
No!

65
00:07:52,055 --> 00:07:54,729
Oh! Oh! I know someone whose
husband just died...

66
00:07:57,394 --> 00:08:00,022
I'm sorry,
I did not see you there.

67
00:08:01,523 --> 00:08:03,321
Or there.

68
00:08:13,201 --> 00:08:15,078
GRU: Kyle? Kyle?

69
00:08:15,453 --> 00:08:17,581
Kyle, no! Do not do your
business on the petunias!

70
00:08:20,500 --> 00:08:22,923
There you go.
Those are Fred's, go crazy.

71
00:08:26,589 --> 00:08:28,387
Good boy!

72
00:08:28,508 --> 00:08:29,600
LUCY: Mr. Gru?

73
00:08:29,676 --> 00:08:30,848
I didn't...
What? Yes?

74
00:08:32,762 --> 00:08:35,936
Hi! Agent Lucy Wilde
of the AVL.

75
00:08:36,182 --> 00:08:39,277
Oh,

76
00:08:39,394 --> 00:08:41,738
Sorry, you're gonna
have to come with me.

77
00:08:41,813 --> 00:08:44,282
Oh, sorry, I...
Freeze ray!

78
00:08:48,194 --> 00:08:50,071
You know, you really
should announce

79
00:08:50,155 --> 00:08:52,123
your weapons after
you fire them, Mr. Gru.

80
00:08:52,323 --> 00:08:53,700
For example...

81
00:08:56,453 --> 00:08:58,672
Lipstick taser!

82
00:08:59,456 --> 00:09:01,379
Oh, it works so good.

83
00:09:10,425 --> 00:09:12,052
Man!

84
00:09:13,011 --> 00:09:15,309
Large person.

85
00:09:21,978 --> 00:09:23,776
Oh, sorry.

86
00:09:27,692 --> 00:09:29,820
Get in there...
Huh?

87
00:09:29,944 --> 00:09:32,663
You big man!

88
00:09:38,203 --> 00:09:39,580
Boss!

89
00:09:53,635 --> 00:09:54,682
Uh? Huh!

90
00:09:59,474 --> 00:10:00,851
Whoa!

91
00:10:02,393 --> 00:10:03,440
Huh?

92
00:10:03,520 --> 00:10:05,193
Ah! Whoo!

93
00:10:05,855 --> 00:10:07,482
Ooh!

94
00:10:26,042 --> 00:10:27,214
Oh!

95
00:10:28,503 --> 00:10:30,631
Huh? Ah. Quack, quack!

96
00:11:42,285 --> 00:11:44,003
MINIONS: Wow!

97
00:12:29,207 --> 00:12:31,255
What? Where?

98
00:12:31,417 --> 00:12:34,261
Whoa, foot is asleep.

99
00:12:34,379 --> 00:12:37,474
Ah, pins and needles!

100
00:12:37,548 --> 00:12:39,391
SILAS: Good afternoon
Mr. Gru.

101
00:12:39,509 --> 00:12:40,556
Eh.

102
00:12:40,677 --> 00:12:43,521
I apologize for our methods
in getting you here.

103
00:12:43,638 --> 00:12:46,266
I don't. I'd do it
again in a heartbeat.

104
00:12:46,349 --> 00:12:48,022
I am not gonna lie,
I enjoyed that.

105
00:12:48,142 --> 00:12:50,736
Every second of it. Gave me
a bit of a buzz, actually.

106
00:12:50,853 --> 00:12:52,571
That's enough, Agent Wilde.

107
00:12:52,647 --> 00:12:53,944
Sorry, sir.

108
00:12:54,023 --> 00:12:55,570
Okay, this is bogus!

109
00:12:56,943 --> 00:12:59,822
I don't know who you people
think you are, but...

110
00:12:59,904 --> 00:13:02,373
We are
the Anti-Villain League.

111
00:13:02,448 --> 00:13:07,921
An ultra-secret organization dedicated
to fighting crime on a global scale.

112
00:13:08,162 --> 00:13:13,134
Rob a bank, we're not interested.
Kill someone, not our deal.

113
00:13:13,209 --> 00:13:18,056
But you want to melt the polar ice
caps, or vaporize Mount Fuji,

114
00:13:18,214 --> 00:13:21,809
or even steal the Moon...

115
00:13:22,176 --> 00:13:24,224
Then we notice.

116
00:13:24,429 --> 00:13:27,273
First of all, you got
no proof that I did that.

117
00:13:27,432 --> 00:13:31,187
Second, after I did
do that, I put it back!

118
00:13:31,311 --> 00:13:32,984
We're well aware of that,
Mr. Gru.

119
00:13:33,062 --> 00:13:35,064
That's why we brought you here.

120
00:13:35,231 --> 00:13:39,202
I am the League's director,
Silas Ramsbottom.

121
00:13:39,902 --> 00:13:40,903
Bottom.

122
00:13:43,906 --> 00:13:46,534
Hilarious.

123
00:13:46,617 --> 00:13:48,290
Agent Wilde?

124
00:13:48,411 --> 00:13:49,754
Oh, me now? Ah.

125
00:13:49,954 --> 00:13:51,831
Um, recently,
an entire top-secret lab

126
00:13:51,914 --> 00:13:53,791
disappeared from
the Arctic Circle.

127
00:13:53,875 --> 00:13:57,379
Yeah, the entire lab, just...

128
00:13:57,462 --> 00:13:59,590
Gone. Where did it go?

129
00:13:59,714 --> 00:14:01,091
I don't care.

130
00:14:01,215 --> 00:14:03,684
Hmm. The lab was
devoted to experiments

131
00:14:03,760 --> 00:14:07,014
involving PX-41,
a transmutation serum.

132
00:14:07,180 --> 00:14:11,105
What is PX-41, you ask?
Mmm, it's pretty bad. Look.

133
00:14:20,777 --> 00:14:22,279
Ah!

134
00:14:30,953 --> 00:14:33,752
Huh, you usually don't
see that in bunnies.

135
00:14:33,831 --> 00:14:37,836
As you can see, in the wrong
hands, the PX-41 serum

136
00:14:37,919 --> 00:14:41,014
could be the most devastating
weapon on Earth.

137
00:14:42,465 --> 00:14:47,266
Fortunately, it has a very
distinct chemical footprint.

138
00:14:47,345 --> 00:14:50,440
And using the latest
chem-tracking technology,

139
00:14:50,556 --> 00:14:53,685
we found traces of it
in the Paradise Mall.

140
00:14:53,810 --> 00:14:55,153
A mall?

141
00:14:55,269 --> 00:14:57,863
Precisely. And we
believe that one of these

142
00:14:57,939 --> 00:15:00,408
shop owners is
a master criminal.

143
00:15:00,483 --> 00:15:01,700
And that's where you come in.

144
00:15:01,818 --> 00:15:06,164
As an ex-villain, you know how a
villain thinks, how a villain acts.

145
00:15:06,280 --> 00:15:08,248
The plan is to set
you up undercover

146
00:15:08,324 --> 00:15:10,292
at a shop in the mall,
where hopefully...

147
00:15:10,410 --> 00:15:13,289
Okay, I see
where this is going,

148
00:15:13,371 --> 00:15:16,716
with all the Mission:
Impossible stuff, but no. No!

149
00:15:16,833 --> 00:15:20,508
I'm a father now.
And a legitimate businessman.

150
00:15:20,628 --> 00:15:24,303
I am developing a line
of delicious jams and jellies.

151
00:15:25,800 --> 00:15:27,768
"Jams and jellies"?

152
00:15:27,844 --> 00:15:30,768
Oh, attitude!
That's right!

153
00:15:30,847 --> 00:15:32,815
So, thanks, but no thanks.

154
00:15:33,808 --> 00:15:38,689
And here's a tip. Instead of
tasing people and kidnapping them,

155
00:15:38,813 --> 00:15:41,362
maybe you should
just give them a call!

156
00:15:41,566 --> 00:15:43,694
Good day, Mr. Sheepsbutt.

157
00:15:43,818 --> 00:15:45,035
Ramsbottom.

158
00:15:45,194 --> 00:15:47,037
Oh, yeah,
like that's any better.

159
00:16:01,043 --> 00:16:03,216
Look, I probably shouldn't
be saying this,

160
00:16:03,379 --> 00:16:06,223
but your work as a villain
was kind of amazing.

161
00:16:06,382 --> 00:16:10,558
So, if you ever wanna get back
to doing something awesome,

162
00:16:11,387 --> 00:16:13,355
give us a call.

163
00:16:32,575 --> 00:16:34,794
Hey, I told you
guys to get to bed.

164
00:16:34,952 --> 00:16:36,078
Oh, sorry.

165
00:16:36,204 --> 00:16:37,706
So, when you going
on your date?

166
00:16:37,788 --> 00:16:38,960
What?

167
00:16:39,081 --> 00:16:41,129
Remember, Miss Jillian said she
was arranging a date for you.

168
00:16:41,250 --> 00:16:45,255
Yeah, well, she is a nut job,
and I'm not going on any date.

169
00:16:45,463 --> 00:16:47,465
Why not? Are you scared?

170
00:16:54,555 --> 00:16:57,399
Hey, did you guys see
the Moon landing on TV?

171
00:16:57,558 --> 00:17:00,107
Yeah, I can't believe it.
It's so cool!

172
00:17:00,269 --> 00:17:01,646
Excuse me? Lisa?

173
00:17:01,729 --> 00:17:02,981
I was talking to
Billy the other day.

174
00:17:03,105 --> 00:17:04,152
No way!

175
00:17:04,273 --> 00:17:05,570
He is so cute.

176
00:17:05,650 --> 00:17:08,745
Ah. Hey, Lisa,
I was wondering if you...

177
00:17:08,819 --> 00:17:13,074
Ew! Gru touched Lisa!
Gru touched Lisa!

178
00:17:13,282 --> 00:17:14,454
KIDS: Ew!

179
00:17:14,909 --> 00:17:16,832
Lisa's got Gruties!

180
00:17:24,293 --> 00:17:28,093
Scared? Of what? Women?
No! That's bonkers!

181
00:17:28,172 --> 00:17:32,427
I just have no interest in going on
a date, that's all. Case closed.

182
00:17:32,593 --> 00:17:35,847
I'm not scared.
Of women. Or dates.

183
00:17:36,097 --> 00:17:37,565
Let's go to bed.

184
00:17:38,891 --> 00:17:40,359
Good night, Edith.

185
00:17:41,394 --> 00:17:44,068
Good night, Margo.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.

186
00:17:44,146 --> 00:17:46,069
Hold the horses.
Who are you texting?

187
00:17:46,148 --> 00:17:47,775
No one. Just my friend Avery.

188
00:17:47,858 --> 00:17:52,659
Avery. Avery? Is that
a girl's name or a boy's name?

189
00:17:52,780 --> 00:17:54,123
Does it matter?

190
00:17:54,198 --> 00:17:57,543
No, no, it doesn't
matter unless it's a boy!

191
00:17:57,660 --> 00:18:00,004
I know what makes you a boy.

192
00:18:00,162 --> 00:18:01,209
Uh, ooh,

193
00:18:01,330 --> 00:18:03,082
You do?

194
00:18:03,666 --> 00:18:05,339
Your bald head.

195
00:18:06,210 --> 00:18:08,008
Oh, yes.

196
00:18:08,170 --> 00:18:10,172
It's really smooth.

197
00:18:10,298 --> 00:18:13,893
Sometimes I stare at it, and imagine
a little chick popping out.

198
00:18:14,844 --> 00:18:15,891
Peep peep peep-

199
00:18:16,971 --> 00:18:18,848
Good night, Agnes.

200
00:18:20,057 --> 00:18:22,059
Never get older.

201
00:18:56,552 --> 00:18:57,599
Hey, oh!

202
00:18:58,846 --> 00:19:00,063
Uh...

203
00:19:33,547 --> 00:19:35,140
Hey, Tim, nice haircut!

204
00:19:35,257 --> 00:19:39,763
Donnie, hang in there, baby!
It's almost Friday.

205
00:19:39,929 --> 00:19:42,557
So, how's today's batch,
Dr. Nefario?

206
00:19:42,640 --> 00:19:44,358
I developed a new formula

207
00:19:44,433 --> 00:19:46,276
which allowed me
to get every known

208
00:19:46,352 --> 00:19:49,196
kind of berry into
one flavor of jelly.

209
00:19:52,900 --> 00:19:54,368
That tastes good!

210
00:19:54,443 --> 00:19:57,117
I love the flavor of that!

211
00:19:57,196 --> 00:19:58,368
It's horrible, isn't it?

212
00:19:58,447 --> 00:19:59,790
No, no!

213
00:19:59,949 --> 00:20:02,828
Oh, we're making
great progress!

214
00:20:02,910 --> 00:20:04,287
Here, try some of this.

215
00:20:04,453 --> 00:20:05,454
Mmm.

216
00:20:08,624 --> 00:20:09,625
Ah.

217
00:20:15,548 --> 00:20:16,720
Whoa.

218
00:20:16,799 --> 00:20:21,805
Okay, just because everybody hates
it, doesn't mean it's not good!

219
00:20:22,346 --> 00:20:23,723
Listen, Gru.

220
00:20:23,806 --> 00:20:25,399
There's something
I've been meaning

221
00:20:25,474 --> 00:20:27,192
to talk to you
about for some time now.

222
00:20:27,351 --> 00:20:29,103
What'? What's wrong?

223
00:20:29,186 --> 00:20:30,438
Um...

224
00:20:32,273 --> 00:20:34,401
I miss being evil.

225
00:20:34,483 --> 00:20:38,659
Sinister plots, large-scale
crimes, it's what I live for.

226
00:20:38,821 --> 00:20:43,577
I mean, don't you think there's
more to our future than jelly?

227
00:20:43,701 --> 00:20:46,875
Well, I'm also
considering a line of jams.

228
00:20:47,788 --> 00:20:50,337
Um, the thing is, Gru,

229
00:20:51,667 --> 00:20:53,669
I've had an offer of
employment elsewhere.

230
00:20:54,503 --> 00:20:56,096
Dr. Nefario!

231
00:20:56,172 --> 00:20:58,220
Come on, you're kidding, right?

232
00:20:58,340 --> 00:21:00,388
It's a great
opportunity for me.

233
00:21:00,509 --> 00:21:03,262
Bigger lab, more evil,

234
00:21:03,471 --> 00:21:05,189
full dental.

235
00:21:13,939 --> 00:21:14,986
Very well.

236
00:21:15,065 --> 00:21:18,695
Let us give you
the proper send-off.

237
00:21:19,028 --> 00:21:20,405
Minions!

238
00:21:24,450 --> 00:21:29,251
The highest honor
awarded to Dr. Nefario

239
00:21:29,371 --> 00:21:32,170
for your years of service,

240
00:21:32,374 --> 00:21:35,719
the 21-fart gun salute!

241
00:21:45,137 --> 00:21:47,060
Uh, I counted 22.

242
00:21:52,895 --> 00:21:55,239
Farewell, my friends.

243
00:22:13,958 --> 00:22:15,960
This may take a while.

244
00:22:16,502 --> 00:22:18,596
Go about your business.

245
00:22:20,756 --> 00:22:23,430
I miss you already!

246
00:23:04,967 --> 00:23:05,968
Huh?

247
00:23:10,014 --> 00:23:11,106
Huh.

248
00:23:18,522 --> 00:23:20,650
Are you sure we
should be doing this?

249
00:23:20,816 --> 00:23:22,818
Yes, it's for his own good.

250
00:23:22,985 --> 00:23:25,488
Okay,
we need to choose a picture.

251
00:23:25,613 --> 00:23:26,614
AGNES: No.

252
00:23:26,906 --> 00:23:27,998
Scary.

253
00:23:28,240 --> 00:23:29,241
Weird.

254
00:23:31,035 --> 00:23:32,207
What is that?

255
00:23:32,286 --> 00:23:35,005
Good morning, girls! I have
an announcement to make.

256
00:23:35,164 --> 00:23:37,041
Hey, what
celebrity do you look like?

257
00:23:37,166 --> 00:23:39,464
Uh, Bruce Willis.

258
00:23:40,002 --> 00:23:41,128
Mmm, no.

259
00:23:41,503 --> 00:23:42,880
Humpty Dummy!

260
00:23:43,380 --> 00:23:44,506
Ooh, Gollum!

261
00:23:45,883 --> 00:23:47,977
Okay, what are you doing?

262
00:23:48,052 --> 00:23:49,975
We're signing you
up for online dating!

263
00:23:50,054 --> 00:23:52,853
Oh, okay. What? No, no, no.

264
00:23:52,973 --> 00:23:54,816
Oh, come on. It's fun.

265
00:23:54,892 --> 00:23:56,769
And it's time for
you to get out there.

266
00:23:56,852 --> 00:24:00,072
No! Stop! No one is ever
getting out there! Ever!

267
00:24:00,189 --> 00:24:03,363
Oh! Okay, now for
the announcement.

268
00:24:03,484 --> 00:24:05,862
I have accepted a new job.

269
00:24:05,945 --> 00:24:07,197
Whoa! Really?

270
00:24:07,279 --> 00:24:10,783
Yes, I have been recruited
by a top-secret agency

271
00:24:10,866 --> 00:24:13,210
to go undercover
and save the world!

272
00:24:13,285 --> 00:24:14,628
You're gonna be a SPY?

273
00:24:14,703 --> 00:24:16,580
That's right, baby!

274
00:24:16,705 --> 00:24:18,548
Gru's back in the game.

275
00:24:18,624 --> 00:24:22,345
With gadgets and weapons and cool cars.
The whole deal.

276
00:24:22,419 --> 00:24:23,545
Awesome!

277
00:24:23,629 --> 00:24:25,927
Are you really
gonna save the world?

278
00:24:26,048 --> 00:24:29,518
Yes. Yes, I am.

279
00:24:53,200 --> 00:24:54,247
Ah!

280
00:25:00,833 --> 00:25:01,925
Hmm.

281
00:25:02,543 --> 00:25:04,386
"Bake My Day."

282
00:25:05,170 --> 00:25:06,262
Blech.

283
00:25:14,513 --> 00:25:18,734
All right, here is the cupcake
recipe I got off the Internet.

284
00:25:22,938 --> 00:25:25,862
And don't go nuts
with the sprinkles!

285
00:25:47,421 --> 00:25:48,468
Whoo.

286
00:25:48,589 --> 00:25:51,593
I wasn't expecting that.
Or was I?

287
00:25:52,593 --> 00:25:55,972
Ooh. You got a little...

288
00:25:58,140 --> 00:25:59,813
Here, I'll get it.

289
00:25:59,975 --> 00:26:01,227
Oh.

290
00:26:01,310 --> 00:26:02,903
It's just spreading.

291
00:26:02,978 --> 00:26:05,322
All right, all right.
I got it! Stop it!

292
00:26:05,481 --> 00:26:06,824
Oh.

293
00:26:06,899 --> 00:26:07,946
I'll let you get it.

294
00:26:10,194 --> 00:26:11,867
Yeah, what you just
saw there was a little

295
00:26:11,945 --> 00:26:13,618
something new
I've been working on.

296
00:26:13,697 --> 00:26:17,622
It's a combination of Jujitsu,
Krav Maga, Aztec warfare

297
00:26:17,701 --> 00:26:19,874
and krumping.

298
00:26:19,995 --> 00:26:22,669
Okay, that's weird.
Why are you here?

299
00:26:22,790 --> 00:26:25,418
On assignment from Silas.
I'm your new partner.

300
00:26:25,501 --> 00:26:26,753
Yay!

301
00:26:26,960 --> 00:26:29,509
What? No, no "yay-"

302
00:26:29,588 --> 00:26:32,262
Ramsbottom didn't say anything
about a partner.

303
00:26:32,341 --> 00:26:34,341
Well, it seems that because
of your checkered past,

304
00:26:34,343 --> 00:26:36,095
everyone else
refused to work with you.

305
00:26:36,178 --> 00:26:38,556
But not me. I stepped up.

306
00:26:38,722 --> 00:26:42,192
And I'm new, so I kind of have
to do what they tell me anyway.

307
00:26:42,726 --> 00:26:43,898
Walla!

308
00:26:46,313 --> 00:26:47,360
Ya!

309
00:26:47,481 --> 00:26:48,824
Aah!

310
00:26:49,024 --> 00:26:50,321
Do you know this guy?

311
00:26:50,442 --> 00:26:52,490
Yes, he's one of my minions.

312
00:26:52,903 --> 00:26:54,405
Oh, I'm sorry.

313
00:26:54,905 --> 00:26:56,532
I should have known.

314
00:26:56,698 --> 00:26:58,371
You are free to go.

315
00:27:03,747 --> 00:27:06,751
Uh? Ah!

316
00:27:14,091 --> 00:27:15,138
Kampai!

317
00:27:29,815 --> 00:27:30,862
Oh!

318
00:27:30,941 --> 00:27:32,033
GRU: Dave...

319
00:27:33,402 --> 00:27:35,279
Earth to Dave!

320
00:27:35,404 --> 00:27:36,576
Huh?

321
00:27:36,697 --> 00:27:38,165
You can leave now.

322
00:27:38,240 --> 00:27:39,287
Oh, uh...

323
00:27:46,790 --> 00:27:49,134
GRU: So, what do we got?
Who's on the list?

324
00:27:49,293 --> 00:27:50,545
Fire them at me.

325
00:27:50,752 --> 00:27:53,676
First suspect,
Hedda Blumentoft,

326
00:27:53,755 --> 00:27:55,632
proprietor of Mum's
the Word Floral Shop.

327
00:27:55,716 --> 00:27:57,514
No, not her.

328
00:27:57,676 --> 00:27:59,223
Okay, moving on...

329
00:27:59,344 --> 00:28:02,143
Chuck Kinney,
owner of Stuff-A-Bear.

330
00:28:04,266 --> 00:28:05,313
Ooh.

331
00:28:05,475 --> 00:28:06,601
I don't think so.

332
00:28:07,269 --> 00:28:08,566
EDUARDO: Hello?

333
00:28:11,899 --> 00:28:14,448
Buenos dias, my friends!

334
00:28:14,610 --> 00:28:17,238
I am Eduardo Perez,

335
00:28:17,404 --> 00:28:20,624
owner of Salsa y Salsa
restaurant, across the mall.

336
00:28:20,782 --> 00:28:23,752
Now open for breakfast.
And you are?

337
00:28:23,911 --> 00:28:26,630
Gru. And this is Lucy.
And we are closed.

338
00:28:26,788 --> 00:28:28,916
This is just going
to take un momento.

339
00:28:29,082 --> 00:28:31,460
I am throwing a big
Cinco de Mayo party,

340
00:28:31,627 --> 00:28:35,632
and I am going to need
200 of your best cupcakes

341
00:28:35,756 --> 00:28:39,556
decorated with
the Mexican flag.

342
00:28:39,635 --> 00:28:41,353
It looks something like this.

343
00:28:42,971 --> 00:28:44,348
What do you think?

344
00:28:44,514 --> 00:28:46,312
LUCY: Ooh.
GRU: on.

345
00:28:46,433 --> 00:28:47,559
Look away!

346
00:28:47,643 --> 00:28:48,644
You, whoo.

347
00:28:49,937 --> 00:28:53,817
Anyway, I have to go. It's all settled.
I'll pick them up next week!

348
00:28:53,982 --> 00:28:57,828
Have a good day. Come by
if you get a chance, okay?

349
00:29:01,031 --> 00:29:04,581
And welcome to the mall family.

350
00:29:12,167 --> 00:29:13,635
El Macho.

351
00:29:14,086 --> 00:29:15,087
What?

352
00:29:15,170 --> 00:29:16,342
But it couldn't be.

353
00:29:16,463 --> 00:29:18,010
What? What couldn't be?

354
00:29:19,174 --> 00:29:24,556
That guy looks exactly like
a villain named El Macho.

355
00:29:24,680 --> 00:29:26,523
From about 20 years ago.

356
00:29:32,562 --> 00:29:34,030
He was ruthless!

357
00:29:34,189 --> 00:29:35,691
He was dangerous.

358
00:29:35,857 --> 00:29:39,703
And as the name implies,
very macho.

359
00:29:50,038 --> 00:29:55,044
He had a reputation for pulling off
heists using only his bare hands!

360
00:29:57,087 --> 00:30:02,184
But sadly, like all the greats,
El Macho was gone too soon.

361
00:30:02,843 --> 00:30:05,562
He died in the most
macho way possible.

362
00:30:05,637 --> 00:30:07,389
Riding a shark

363
00:30:07,472 --> 00:30:11,648
with 250 pounds of dynamite
strapped to his chest

364
00:30:11,810 --> 00:30:15,906
into the mouth of
an active volcano!

365
00:30:18,442 --> 00:30:19,989
It was glorious.

366
00:30:21,570 --> 00:30:25,245
Yeah, sounds like
El Macho's pretty dead.

367
00:30:25,365 --> 00:30:27,788
They never found the body.
Oh, no.

368
00:30:27,909 --> 00:30:33,086
All that was ever retrieved was
a pile of singed chest hair.

369
00:30:33,248 --> 00:30:36,798
But that face!
It has got to be El Macho!

370
00:30:37,377 --> 00:30:41,257
Then what do you say you and I
break into his restaurant? Tonight?

371
00:30:41,423 --> 00:30:44,051
Yes, that's good,
because I am telling you,

372
00:30:44,134 --> 00:30:48,389
if anybody in this
place has the PX-41 serum,

373
00:30:49,014 --> 00:30:50,641
it's him.

374
00:30:52,934 --> 00:30:56,859
All right, all right, homework done,
pajamas on, teeth brushed, time for bed.

375
00:30:56,938 --> 00:30:58,110
What's the big hurry?

376
00:30:58,273 --> 00:31:00,150
I just have
a lot of work to do.

377
00:31:00,275 --> 00:31:02,198
Work, what kind of work?

378
00:31:02,277 --> 00:31:03,995
Very important business.

379
00:31:04,071 --> 00:31:05,869
So, hugs, kisses.

380
00:31:05,947 --> 00:31:08,791
Good night, sleep tight, don't
let the bedbugs blah-blah-blah.

381
00:31:08,867 --> 00:31:09,914
Whoa!

382
00:31:09,993 --> 00:31:11,370
But you said
you'd help me practice

383
00:31:11,453 --> 00:31:13,547
my part for
the Mother's Day show.

384
00:31:15,123 --> 00:31:18,218
Fine, fine.
Let me hear it. Quickly.

385
00:31:18,377 --> 00:31:22,098
She kisses my boo-boos,
she braids my hair.

386
00:31:22,297 --> 00:31:25,176
My mother is beyond compare.

387
00:31:25,342 --> 00:31:28,221
We love you,
mothers, everywhere.

388
00:31:28,804 --> 00:31:31,648
Wow! That was something else.

389
00:31:31,807 --> 00:31:34,777
I really liked the way
you smiled at the end.

390
00:31:34,935 --> 00:31:36,937
Let's try this one more time,

391
00:31:37,104 --> 00:31:42,201
but a teensy bit less
like a zombie, okay?

392
00:31:42,275 --> 00:31:43,322
Okay.

393
00:31:43,402 --> 00:31:46,451
She kisses my boo-boos,
she braids my hair...

394
00:31:46,530 --> 00:31:48,328
Perfect! Time to go.

395
00:31:48,407 --> 00:31:50,956
I don't think I should do this.

396
00:31:51,034 --> 00:31:53,332
Well, what do you mean?
Why not?

397
00:31:53,412 --> 00:31:55,130
I don't even have a mom.

398
00:31:55,997 --> 00:31:58,591
Well, you don't need
one to do the show.

399
00:31:58,667 --> 00:32:01,420
I mean, you did
the Veterans Day Pageant

400
00:32:01,503 --> 00:32:03,005
and you haven't been in combat.

401
00:32:04,089 --> 00:32:05,511
This is different.

402
00:32:05,674 --> 00:32:10,646
Okay, well, then maybe you can
just use your imagination.

403
00:32:10,804 --> 00:32:13,603
You mean I
pretend I have a mom?

404
00:32:13,723 --> 00:32:16,476
Yes, right?
You can do that, can't you?

405
00:32:16,560 --> 00:32:18,688
Yeah! I do that all the time.

406
00:32:18,812 --> 00:32:20,189
Thanks, Gru!

407
00:32:23,358 --> 00:32:25,952
Hey!

408
00:32:51,845 --> 00:32:54,064
All right. Hey, hey,
no, no! No.

409
00:32:54,181 --> 00:32:56,309
HeY-Hey. please.

410
00:32:56,391 --> 00:32:59,565
Kevin, Jerry,
watch the girls for me, okay?

411
00:32:59,686 --> 00:33:03,065
Dave, Stuart, come this way!
With me! Come on!

412
00:33:05,650 --> 00:33:06,993
Come on!

413
00:33:07,068 --> 00:33:08,069
Mmm-mmm!

414
00:33:38,183 --> 00:33:39,480
Oh!

415
00:33:41,937 --> 00:33:42,984
Mmm-hmm.

416
00:33:46,733 --> 00:33:47,780
Huh?

417
00:33:53,573 --> 00:33:55,621
Ocal O98!

418
00:34:12,509 --> 00:34:13,556
Looka too!

419
00:34:18,848 --> 00:34:19,895
Huh?

420
00:34:59,806 --> 00:35:03,310
We're stealth ninjas.
We make no sound.

421
00:35:03,518 --> 00:35:05,612
Right. Gotcha.

422
00:35:06,521 --> 00:35:08,398
Ya!

423
00:35:10,442 --> 00:35:13,036
All right, El Macho.
You're going down.

424
00:35:13,111 --> 00:35:15,159
Wait! Wait.
What?

425
00:35:16,323 --> 00:35:17,916
What are you doing?

426
00:35:17,991 --> 00:35:20,619
I'm checking for
laser beam alarm triggers.

427
00:35:21,870 --> 00:35:23,122
It's a restaurant!

428
00:35:23,246 --> 00:35:24,766
You never know what
kind of booby traps

429
00:35:24,873 --> 00:35:26,420
this guy could have set.
Huh? Come on.

430
00:35:26,499 --> 00:35:28,843
There are no booby traps.

431
00:35:30,211 --> 00:35:31,929
Ha! Booby!

432
00:35:42,223 --> 00:35:44,567
Oh. There's a chicken.

433
00:35:44,893 --> 00:35:46,941
Are you lost, little guy?

434
00:35:47,062 --> 00:35:48,985
You must be lost.

435
00:35:49,105 --> 00:35:50,948
Ha! Some guard dog.

436
00:35:55,570 --> 00:35:57,743
Get it off of me!
Get it off of me!

437
00:35:58,573 --> 00:35:59,574
Aah!

438
00:36:05,330 --> 00:36:07,003
I got you!

439
00:36:11,920 --> 00:36:13,263
L9ot it!

440
00:36:21,846 --> 00:36:23,223
Ha!

441
00:36:25,058 --> 00:36:26,059
Om

442
00:36:32,440 --> 00:36:34,989
What is wrong
with that chicken?

443
00:36:35,652 --> 00:36:39,623
Hey, that <i>polio</i> es loco

444
00:36:40,115 --> 00:36:41,287
No?

445
00:36:41,408 --> 00:36:43,331
Okay, let's go.

446
00:36:50,291 --> 00:36:52,009
Are you getting anything?

447
00:36:52,085 --> 00:36:53,632
No, not yet.

448
00:36:53,712 --> 00:36:57,512
But, hey, maybe you can find
something with these X-ray goggles.

449
00:36:59,467 --> 00:37:00,514
Bah.

450
00:37:05,390 --> 00:37:07,643
How are they working?
Tell me! Tell me!

451
00:37:07,726 --> 00:37:09,103
Aah! Oof!

452
00:37:09,185 --> 00:37:10,778
What's wrong?
Ls something wrong?

453
00:37:10,854 --> 00:37:14,233
That's an image I'll never
get out of my brain. Blech!

454
00:37:22,323 --> 00:37:24,166
I knew it!

455
00:37:24,325 --> 00:37:26,168
The serum is in here!

456
00:37:26,244 --> 00:37:27,496
Ooh, then let's get it.

457
00:37:29,497 --> 00:37:32,000
This is going to be good!

458
00:37:32,083 --> 00:37:33,130
Ah.

459
00:37:37,046 --> 00:37:38,639
Ah-ha!

460
00:37:38,715 --> 00:37:39,967
What?

461
00:37:41,843 --> 00:37:43,186
Salsa?

462
00:37:43,344 --> 00:37:44,937
Aw, man.

463
00:37:46,556 --> 00:37:47,557
Oh.

464
00:37:50,727 --> 00:37:54,573
Somebody's going
to die tonight.

465
00:38:00,028 --> 00:38:01,826
Pollito!

466
00:38:01,905 --> 00:38:04,328
What did they do to you?
Pollito? Can you hear me?

467
00:38:05,575 --> 00:38:08,954
Who would do this to such
a sweet little chicken?

468
00:38:09,037 --> 00:38:10,960
What? Who's there?

469
00:38:12,749 --> 00:38:14,717
You coming out?
Or am I gonna go in?

470
00:38:19,881 --> 00:38:21,303
Yah!

471
00:38:22,425 --> 00:38:23,472
Huh?

472
00:38:24,636 --> 00:38:25,888
Stop!

473
00:38:26,012 --> 00:38:28,060
My eyes!

474
00:38:29,474 --> 00:38:31,397
Gru, call one of
your munchkins!

475
00:38:32,060 --> 00:38:33,687
We've been spotted!
Come get us!

476
00:38:33,770 --> 00:38:35,147
Huh? Hey!

477
00:38:35,230 --> 00:38:36,732
Ah!

478
00:38:46,741 --> 00:38:48,243
Hmm, subtle.

479
00:38:52,080 --> 00:38:54,299
Over here! Over here!

480
00:38:54,415 --> 00:38:55,962
Over

481
00:38:56,042 --> 00:38:57,168
here.

482
00:39:04,008 --> 00:39:05,260
Hold tight!

483
00:39:09,097 --> 00:39:10,269
Aah!

484
00:39:15,854 --> 00:39:18,607
I have you now!

485
00:39:53,600 --> 00:39:55,477
BOY: Yay! Ice cream!

486
00:39:57,020 --> 00:39:58,067
Huh?

487
00:40:16,372 --> 00:40:18,420
Huh?

488
00:40:53,201 --> 00:40:54,748
LUCY: All right, there he is.

489
00:40:54,911 --> 00:40:57,790
Suspect number eight,
Floyd Eaglesan.

490
00:40:57,956 --> 00:40:59,503
Oh, okay.

491
00:40:59,666 --> 00:41:01,543
See if you can get closer.
Go, go.

492
00:41:12,637 --> 00:41:14,105
All right.

493
00:41:14,222 --> 00:41:15,348
What the...

494
00:41:16,683 --> 00:41:18,685
Oh, no. That's not good.

495
00:41:20,520 --> 00:41:21,521
Whoa!

496
00:41:21,604 --> 00:41:23,072
Hey, uh, what?

497
00:41:25,024 --> 00:41:26,071
Oh!

498
00:41:30,405 --> 00:41:31,998
AGNES: Hey, Gru!

499
00:41:32,073 --> 00:41:34,542
Oh, girls! What are you
doing here?

500
00:41:34,617 --> 00:41:36,585
Well, we thought
we'd come visit you at work.

501
00:41:36,744 --> 00:41:39,418
So, you're saving the world
in a garbage can?

502
00:41:40,957 --> 00:41:42,004
Funny.

503
00:41:42,083 --> 00:41:43,926
Hey! There you are.

504
00:41:44,043 --> 00:41:45,420
Oh. Who's this?

505
00:41:45,586 --> 00:41:49,591
Lucy, these are my girls,
Margo, Edith and Agnes.

506
00:41:49,716 --> 00:41:52,560
Girls, Lucy. Lucy, girls.

507
00:41:52,635 --> 00:41:54,603
Hello.
Hi.

508
00:42:02,937 --> 00:42:04,405
Are you single?

509
00:42:05,440 --> 00:42:06,612
Oh! Goodness.

510
00:42:06,691 --> 00:42:10,741
Oh, hey! I have an idea. Since Lucy
and I have lots of work to do,

511
00:42:10,862 --> 00:42:13,490
why don't you girls go and
explore the mall? Bye!

512
00:42:13,698 --> 00:42:16,793
Here is some money, go buy
some useless mall junk.

513
00:42:16,951 --> 00:42:18,544
Some headbands and...

514
00:42:18,661 --> 00:42:20,129
Are you gonna marry Lucy?

515
00:42:20,288 --> 00:42:24,168
Are you out of your gourd?
No! She just works with me.

516
00:42:24,292 --> 00:42:25,669
Plus, you love her.

517
00:42:25,752 --> 00:42:28,471
You love her! You love her!
You really, really love her!

518
00:42:28,629 --> 00:42:29,801
And you're gonna get married!

519
00:42:29,881 --> 00:42:30,973
Okay, stop.
This is a song of lies.

520
00:42:31,049 --> 00:42:32,209
And I will be the flower girl!

521
00:42:32,216 --> 00:42:34,264
I don't even like her.
Now, go have fun!

522
00:42:36,220 --> 00:42:38,348
Almost forgot. Hugs!

523
00:42:38,431 --> 00:42:39,933
Good luck saving the world.
Bye.

524
00:42:40,016 --> 00:42:41,313
AGNES: Bye, Gru!

525
00:42:45,646 --> 00:42:48,946
Kids, right? They're funny.

526
00:42:49,025 --> 00:42:50,993
Those girls totally adore you.

527
00:42:51,069 --> 00:42:52,821
I bet you're a fun dad.

528
00:42:53,488 --> 00:42:54,580
Huh.

529
00:42:54,655 --> 00:42:56,657
I am pretty fun.

530
00:43:05,625 --> 00:43:07,002
Is that stealing?

531
00:43:07,126 --> 00:43:10,005
Not if my wish was that I would
get a lot of free coins.

532
00:43:37,949 --> 00:43:39,292
Whoa!

533
00:43:41,202 --> 00:43:42,704
Cool glasses.

534
00:43:42,912 --> 00:43:43,959
Oh.

535
00:43:44,664 --> 00:43:46,132
I'm Antonio.

536
00:43:46,374 --> 00:43:48,217
I'm Margo.

537
00:43:48,376 --> 00:43:51,971
I was just going to get a cookie.
Care to join me?

538
00:43:52,046 --> 00:43:54,014
Uh, sure.

539
00:43:54,465 --> 00:43:56,809
I'm Margo.

540
00:44:04,767 --> 00:44:06,986
Um, I'll catch up
with you guys later.

541
00:44:07,061 --> 00:44:08,404
Bye!

542
00:44:10,148 --> 00:44:12,526
Can I be
the first to say, "Ew!"

543
00:44:12,608 --> 00:44:14,485
We gotta go tell Gru!

544
00:44:19,198 --> 00:44:20,791
All right, I'm going in.

545
00:44:20,950 --> 00:44:23,950
LUCY: If it picks up any traces of the
serum, the sensor in your belt buckle

546
00:44:23,995 --> 00:44:25,372
will make a sound like this...

547
00:44:25,454 --> 00:44:26,706
Mee-maw! Mee-maw!

548
00:44:26,831 --> 00:44:27,832
Mee-ma W! Mee-ma w!
Okay!

549
00:44:27,915 --> 00:44:29,667
I get it. I get it.

550
00:44:36,549 --> 00:44:39,974
Welcome to Eagle Hair Club.

551
00:44:40,094 --> 00:44:42,643
It's about time you showed up,

552
00:44:42,805 --> 00:44:44,102
Mr. Gru.

553
00:44:45,433 --> 00:44:47,356
You know my name?

554
00:44:48,603 --> 00:44:51,948
When someone moves into the mall
who is folically-challenged,

555
00:44:52,064 --> 00:44:55,614
I make it my business
to know all about them.

556
00:44:55,776 --> 00:44:58,450
You are bald, and that is bad.

557
00:44:59,655 --> 00:45:01,282
There you go, my sweet.

558
00:45:01,365 --> 00:45:03,242
LUCY: I'm getting
nothing so far.

559
00:45:03,326 --> 00:45:04,953
I think you need
to move around.

560
00:45:12,710 --> 00:45:15,429
Wow, this looks interesting.
What is it?

561
00:45:15,588 --> 00:45:17,090
I take it you're an art lover?

562
00:45:17,256 --> 00:45:18,303
LUCY: No serum.

563
00:45:18,382 --> 00:45:19,599
Yeah, not so much.

564
00:45:23,387 --> 00:45:26,357
Oh, how about this
impressive trinket?

565
00:45:26,474 --> 00:45:28,272
I'd hardly call it
a trinket, Mr. Gru.

566
00:45:28,351 --> 00:45:29,853
LUCY: Nothing.
The International...

567
00:45:29,936 --> 00:45:31,062
Yeah, I don't care.

568
00:45:37,235 --> 00:45:38,236
LUCY: Mee-maw! Mee-maw!

569
00:45:38,319 --> 00:45:40,742
LUCY: Hold on, I'm picking up something.
Behind that wall!

570
00:45:40,821 --> 00:45:42,494
Ah, and what do we have here?

571
00:45:42,573 --> 00:45:45,827
These are my trial wigs.
You should take one.

572
00:45:45,910 --> 00:45:49,164
No, thanks. So, what's on
the other side of the wall?

573
00:45:49,288 --> 00:45:50,585
Here you are!
Look at me! Focus!

574
00:45:50,665 --> 00:45:51,837
LUCY: Gru?

575
00:45:51,916 --> 00:45:56,422
I promise that this wig will
transform you from ugly

576
00:45:56,504 --> 00:45:59,599
to irresistible.

577
00:46:00,216 --> 00:46:01,843
AGNES: Margo has a boyfriend!

578
00:46:01,926 --> 00:46:03,928
And they're going on a date!

579
00:46:04,011 --> 00:46:05,354
Date? Boyfriend?

580
00:46:05,429 --> 00:46:06,681
What?

581
00:46:19,068 --> 00:46:20,194
There she goes!

582
00:46:32,164 --> 00:46:33,882
Oh, you're so funny.

583
00:46:34,041 --> 00:46:35,133
Gross!

584
00:46:35,334 --> 00:46:37,382
Look, they're in love.
Oh, no, no, no.

585
00:46:37,503 --> 00:46:39,881
Do not say that. No, no, no.

586
00:46:39,964 --> 00:46:44,310
And my dream is to one day
play video games for a living.

587
00:46:44,385 --> 00:46:46,137
Wow.

588
00:46:46,220 --> 00:46:48,268
You're so complicated.

589
00:46:48,389 --> 00:46:49,936
Margo.

590
00:46:50,057 --> 00:46:51,604
What is going on here?

591
00:46:52,184 --> 00:46:56,485
Oh, Gru, se llama Antonio.
Me llamo Margo.

592
00:46:56,564 --> 00:46:59,909
Me llama-lama ding-dong.
Who cares? Let's go.

593
00:47:05,865 --> 00:47:06,912
MARGO: Whoa!

594
00:47:30,681 --> 00:47:32,399
Kids eat free on Tuesdays.

595
00:47:42,443 --> 00:47:43,865
Yay, POP!

596
00:47:43,944 --> 00:47:45,571
MARGO: That's awesome!

597
00:47:47,448 --> 00:47:51,123
So good to see you again, mi compadre!
Ha! Yeah.

598
00:47:51,202 --> 00:47:53,671
Oh, I see you have
already met my father.

599
00:47:53,829 --> 00:47:55,923
What? Father?

600
00:47:55,998 --> 00:47:59,423
Si. Look at this crazy
small world we live in, eh?

601
00:47:59,502 --> 00:48:01,504
Come, sit,
let me get you something.

602
00:48:03,255 --> 00:48:05,349
Oh, look at you. Heh?

603
00:48:06,884 --> 00:48:09,728
He likes me.

604
00:48:09,804 --> 00:48:13,684
Oh, oh! I'm sorry. Pollito
is usually very friendly.

605
00:48:13,766 --> 00:48:15,359
He had a rough night.

606
00:48:18,896 --> 00:48:21,615
Well, we really should be going.
Girls, come on.

607
00:48:21,732 --> 00:48:23,484
That is a pity.

608
00:48:23,567 --> 00:48:26,286
Young love is beautiful, no?

609
00:48:26,404 --> 00:48:27,656
No!

610
00:48:27,738 --> 00:48:31,333
You know, they're not in love.
They hardly know each other.

611
00:48:32,159 --> 00:48:34,332
You are right, Cabeza de huevo.

612
00:48:34,412 --> 00:48:36,665
They must get to
know each other better!

613
00:48:36,831 --> 00:48:40,881
Antonio, why don't you invite
your girlfriend and her family

614
00:48:40,960 --> 00:48:42,587
to our Cinco de Mayo party?

615
00:48:42,670 --> 00:48:43,717
No, no.

616
00:48:43,838 --> 00:48:44,930
BOTH: Si!

617
00:48:59,728 --> 00:49:02,026
I'm sorry, El Macho?

618
00:49:02,106 --> 00:49:04,154
Hadn't we
eliminated him as a suspect

619
00:49:04,275 --> 00:49:06,277
after the whole salsa incident?

620
00:49:06,360 --> 00:49:08,863
Yes, but there has
been a new development,

621
00:49:08,946 --> 00:49:12,041
and I'm telling you,
this is the guy.

622
00:49:12,116 --> 00:49:14,539
You need to
arrest him immediately.

623
00:49:14,618 --> 00:49:18,122
And his deviously charming son!

624
00:49:18,205 --> 00:49:21,129
I'm pretty sure that
the son is involved, too.

625
00:49:21,208 --> 00:49:23,882
The son, also!
You got to get the son!

626
00:49:24,003 --> 00:49:27,553
I think that
the son is the mastermind!

627
00:49:27,631 --> 00:49:30,180
There's a look,
there's a devilish look

628
00:49:30,259 --> 00:49:31,806
in his eyes,
and I don't like it!

629
00:49:31,886 --> 00:49:33,980
Yes, but I don't
really see any evidence.

630
00:49:34,096 --> 00:49:35,814
Evidence, schmevidence.
I go with my gut,

631
00:49:35,890 --> 00:49:39,565
and my gut tells me
that this guy is El Macho.

632
00:49:39,643 --> 00:49:42,146
Lock him up, lock up the son.

633
00:49:42,229 --> 00:49:46,234
Don't forget about the son.
The kid gives me the creeps!

634
00:49:46,400 --> 00:49:48,323
Oh, dear, oh, dear, oh, dear.

635
00:49:48,402 --> 00:49:53,408
But, on the less
crazy side of things,

636
00:49:53,574 --> 00:49:56,703
Gru discovered traces of the
serum at Eagle Hair Club!

637
00:49:57,369 --> 00:49:59,042
Hmm, interesting.

638
00:49:59,121 --> 00:50:01,340
Yeah! And you know
who made that happen'? Huh?

639
00:50:01,415 --> 00:50:04,715
This guy.
Nailed it. Amazing, right?

640
00:50:04,793 --> 00:50:08,593
No, I mean, sure. But it's
not him, it is El Macho!

641
00:50:08,714 --> 00:50:10,591
Mr. Gru, please!

642
00:50:10,758 --> 00:50:13,602
No! It is him,
and I will prove it!

643
00:50:15,095 --> 00:50:17,268
Gru, come on!

644
00:50:19,892 --> 00:50:22,065
He really thinks it's El Macho.

645
00:50:22,937 --> 00:50:24,280
Can you tell?

646
00:50:48,796 --> 00:50:50,423
Oh. VVhoo!

647
00:51:27,543 --> 00:51:28,840
Give me that!

648
00:51:37,011 --> 00:51:39,890
Kevin, the Wi-Fi's out!

649
00:51:40,180 --> 00:51:41,773
Kevin?

650
00:51:41,932 --> 00:51:44,526
Hey, Lance,
where the heck is Kevin?

651
00:51:45,769 --> 00:51:50,195
All right, we need to revisit the
number of vacation days you guys get.

652
00:51:50,274 --> 00:51:52,652
I can't find anybody anymore.

653
00:51:53,360 --> 00:51:55,454
JILLIANI Gru, it's Jillian!

654
00:51:56,447 --> 00:51:58,370
I've got good news!

655
00:51:58,532 --> 00:52:00,660
I have my friend
Shannon here with me.

656
00:52:00,743 --> 00:52:02,871
I was thinking you
two could get some grub.

657
00:52:02,953 --> 00:52:06,378
You know, tear it up, see what happens!

658
00:52:06,540 --> 00:52:07,541
Open Up!

659
00:52:07,625 --> 00:52:09,172
La, la, la, la, la, la, la...

660
00:52:09,251 --> 00:52:12,175
Agnes! Agnes,
tell Jillian I'm not here.

661
00:52:12,963 --> 00:52:14,385
Gru's not here.

662
00:52:14,548 --> 00:52:16,221
Are you sure?

663
00:52:16,342 --> 00:52:17,810
Yes, he just told me!

664
00:52:17,885 --> 00:52:19,933
Mmm-mmm!

665
00:52:20,429 --> 00:52:22,477
I mean,
no, he didn'tjust tell me.

666
00:52:22,598 --> 00:52:25,693
Agnes, where is Gru?

667
00:52:27,061 --> 00:52:28,938
He's putting on lipstick!

668
00:52:30,230 --> 00:52:31,903
He's swatting at flies!

669
00:52:32,024 --> 00:52:33,071
No! No!

670
00:52:33,150 --> 00:52:34,652
He's chopping his head off!

671
00:52:36,737 --> 00:52:39,115
He's pooping?

672
00:52:39,823 --> 00:52:41,917
I know you're in there, Gru!

673
00:52:42,076 --> 00:52:45,455
There's no way you're
getting out of this!

674
00:52:50,918 --> 00:52:54,047
SHANNON: I have to tell you, I
was so nervous about tonight.

675
00:52:54,129 --> 00:52:57,349
I mean there's just so
many phonies out there!

676
00:52:58,008 --> 00:53:00,852
Yes, I hear you.

677
00:53:01,679 --> 00:53:03,397
Oh, so, do you work out?

678
00:53:03,472 --> 00:53:04,564
Well...

679
00:53:04,640 --> 00:53:07,519
I mean, obviously, you
don't, but would you consider it'?

680
00:53:07,643 --> 00:53:11,273
Huh? Physical fitness is
very important to Shannon.

681
00:53:11,355 --> 00:53:13,153
As you can tell,
right? Huh?

682
00:53:14,316 --> 00:53:15,408
Ah.

683
00:53:15,484 --> 00:53:16,610
I can tell.

684
00:53:16,735 --> 00:53:17,861
Solid.

685
00:53:17,945 --> 00:53:20,539
We are in the restaurant,
you know.

686
00:53:22,449 --> 00:53:23,951
Hi. Takeout for Lucy?

687
00:53:24,076 --> 00:53:25,578
Sure, just a sec.

688
00:53:37,548 --> 00:53:40,848
SHANNON: Your accent
is so exotic.

689
00:53:40,926 --> 00:53:43,145
Ah. Well, thank you very much.

690
00:53:43,220 --> 00:53:44,893
I know someone who
can fix that for you.

691
00:53:44,972 --> 00:53:47,816
And you'll be
talking normal in no time!

692
00:53:50,144 --> 00:53:52,317
Whoo. Is it hot in here?

693
00:53:54,231 --> 00:53:56,029
How's the food?

694
00:53:57,067 --> 00:54:00,788
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Are you wearing a wig?

695
00:54:00,904 --> 00:54:02,030
What?

696
00:54:02,114 --> 00:54:04,082
Ah! I don't think so.

697
00:54:04,158 --> 00:54:05,330
I knew it.

698
00:54:05,451 --> 00:54:07,579
You're a phony.
I hate phonies!

699
00:54:07,661 --> 00:54:09,880
Oh, what?
No. These locks are all mine.

700
00:54:09,955 --> 00:54:11,252
No, they're not!

701
00:54:11,331 --> 00:54:14,460
You know what I'm gonna do? I'm
gonna rip that thing off your head,

702
00:54:14,543 --> 00:54:17,422
and show everyone what a
bald-headed phony you are.

703
00:54:17,504 --> 00:54:18,721
I don't think so, Miss Lady.

704
00:54:28,474 --> 00:54:29,726
Hello?

705
00:54:29,808 --> 00:54:31,151
Hello? Are you...

706
00:54:31,226 --> 00:54:32,478
LUCY: Hey, Gru.

707
00:54:32,561 --> 00:54:35,690
Hello, Lucy.
How are you doing?

708
00:54:35,773 --> 00:54:38,196
Wow, looks like your
date's out for the count.

709
00:54:38,275 --> 00:54:41,279
It's like she's been shot with
a mild moose tranquilizer.

710
00:54:47,159 --> 00:54:50,003
Yeah, I'm winking because
that's what actually happened.

711
00:54:50,078 --> 00:54:53,298
Scusi, what's happening here?
She no like?

712
00:54:53,373 --> 00:54:54,841
Oh, she's just, uh...

713
00:54:56,335 --> 00:54:57,461
Oh, ho.

714
00:54:57,544 --> 00:54:59,512
Si, sf. Si.

715
00:54:59,588 --> 00:55:01,010
Shall we take her home?

716
00:55:12,059 --> 00:55:13,231
Oh!

717
00:55:43,465 --> 00:55:46,935
Well, I think you did it. You just
officially had the worst date ever.

718
00:55:47,052 --> 00:55:48,599
Huh, tell me about it.

719
00:55:48,971 --> 00:55:52,191
Don't worry. It can only get
better from here, right?

720
00:55:52,266 --> 00:55:54,394
But if it doesn't, you can
always borrow my dart gun.

721
00:55:54,476 --> 00:55:56,854
I've had to use it on
one or two dates myself.

722
00:55:56,979 --> 00:55:59,198
Yeah, you know,
as far as dates go,

723
00:55:59,273 --> 00:56:01,617
I think I'm good
with just the one.

724
00:56:05,487 --> 00:56:08,491
Well, good night, partner.

725
00:56:10,826 --> 00:56:12,078
This was fun.

726
00:56:12,160 --> 00:56:15,004
Yes. Surprisingly, it was.

727
00:56:15,497 --> 00:56:17,966
Oh, and, uh,
just between you and me?

728
00:56:18,542 --> 00:56:20,419
You look much better bald.

729
00:56:22,838 --> 00:56:24,306
See you tomorrow.

730
00:56:33,473 --> 00:56:35,066
Quack, quack, quack,
quack, quack!

731
00:56:40,564 --> 00:56:41,781
Yay!

732
00:56:41,857 --> 00:56:43,484
So, I take it
the date went well?

733
00:56:43,567 --> 00:56:45,820
No, it was horrible.

734
00:56:56,622 --> 00:56:59,000
High-five!

735
00:56:59,917 --> 00:57:01,214
Bump it.

736
00:57:43,460 --> 00:57:45,258
Mr. Ramsbottom?

737
00:57:45,379 --> 00:57:46,596
Oh, hello.

738
00:57:46,713 --> 00:57:48,135
What are you doing here?

739
00:57:48,215 --> 00:57:50,138
We got him.
Got who?

740
00:57:50,258 --> 00:57:51,931
Floyd Eaglesan!

741
00:57:52,052 --> 00:57:54,976
Our agents located a secret
room in his shop last night

742
00:57:55,055 --> 00:57:56,853
and discovered this.

743
00:57:56,932 --> 00:58:01,062
It's empty, but we found traces
of the PX-41 serum in it.

744
00:58:01,228 --> 00:58:02,571
He's our man.

745
00:58:02,688 --> 00:58:07,068
So, somehow, in spite of your
incompetence, we solved this one.

746
00:58:07,192 --> 00:58:08,739
I was framed!

747
00:58:08,819 --> 00:58:10,412
You won't get away with this!

748
00:58:10,487 --> 00:58:13,036
Get your mitts off of me!
Lam a legitimate businessman.

749
00:58:13,115 --> 00:58:16,870
Ah. All right. So what now?

750
00:58:16,952 --> 00:58:20,047
Well, now you're free to
go back to your business.

751
00:58:20,163 --> 00:58:22,586
Mmm. Jams and jellies.

752
00:58:22,708 --> 00:58:24,676
And it looks like
Agent Wilde will be

753
00:58:24,751 --> 00:58:26,719
transferring to our
Australian branch.

754
00:58:27,421 --> 00:58:28,638
Australia?

755
00:58:28,714 --> 00:58:29,931
Yes.

756
00:58:30,090 --> 00:58:31,763
But thank you for everything.

757
00:58:31,842 --> 00:58:34,686
And by everything,
of course I mean nothing.

758
00:58:34,761 --> 00:58:37,355
Toodle pip and cheerio,
Mr. Gru.

759
00:58:41,852 --> 00:58:44,071
Hey, there.
Hey.

760
00:58:44,146 --> 00:58:45,568
So, we got him.

761
00:58:45,647 --> 00:58:48,776
Yay. That's great.

762
00:58:48,900 --> 00:58:50,698
And now you're
going to Australia?

763
00:58:50,777 --> 00:58:53,530
Well, it's not definite yet.
I'm still figuring it out.

764
00:58:53,613 --> 00:58:55,741
I've already been
working on my accent.

765
00:58:55,824 --> 00:58:57,997
Wallaby. Didgeridoo.

766
00:58:58,118 --> 00:59:00,792
Hugh Jackman.

767
00:59:01,163 --> 00:59:04,758
So, um... Pretty excited.

768
00:59:05,625 --> 00:59:07,093
Great.

769
00:59:07,169 --> 00:59:09,467
Well, good luck.

770
00:59:09,588 --> 00:59:12,341
Thanks. You, too.

771
00:59:13,133 --> 00:59:15,807
Oh! Here.
I wanted to give you this.

772
00:59:15,969 --> 00:59:17,812
Your lipstick taser?

773
00:59:17,888 --> 00:59:19,811
Yeah, it's just a memento.

774
00:59:19,890 --> 00:59:23,986
Just, you know,
from the first time we met.

775
00:59:24,144 --> 00:59:26,317
Oh. Thank you, Lucy.

776
00:59:27,147 --> 00:59:28,649
SILAS: Agent Wilde.

777
00:59:29,107 --> 00:59:32,236
Well, it looks like
they need you, so...

778
00:59:32,319 --> 00:59:35,118
Yeah, I better go.

779
00:59:36,198 --> 00:59:37,575
Bye, Gru.

780
01:00:14,069 --> 01:00:16,037
I brought you an umbrella.

781
01:00:19,908 --> 01:00:21,000
Ah, thank you.

782
01:00:21,076 --> 01:00:22,669
What are you doing out here?

783
01:00:23,245 --> 01:00:27,375
Remember when you
said that I liked Lucy?

784
01:00:28,083 --> 01:00:31,007
Well, it turns out,

785
01:00:31,169 --> 01:00:32,386
you're right.

786
01:00:33,130 --> 01:00:34,222
Really?

787
01:00:34,381 --> 01:00:35,758
Yes, but...

788
01:00:36,341 --> 01:00:38,890
Well, she's moving away.

789
01:00:38,969 --> 01:00:41,768
I'm never going
to see her again.

790
01:00:45,517 --> 01:00:47,611
Is there anything
I could do to help?

791
01:00:48,186 --> 01:00:51,941
Aw, I don't... I don't
think so, sweetheart.

792
01:00:52,774 --> 01:00:55,573
Well, is there
anything you could do?

793
01:00:57,195 --> 01:00:59,823
Hello, Lucy. This is Gru.

794
01:00:59,906 --> 01:01:03,001
I know up to this
point our relationship

795
01:01:03,076 --> 01:01:05,420
has been strictly professional,

796
01:01:05,495 --> 01:01:09,796
and you're leaving for
Australia and all, but...

797
01:01:09,958 --> 01:01:13,007
Okay, here is the question.

798
01:01:13,170 --> 01:01:14,763
Would you like to...

799
01:01:16,131 --> 01:01:19,431
To go out on a date?

800
01:01:20,260 --> 01:01:21,933
Uh, no.

801
01:01:22,053 --> 01:01:23,976
Okay, that's not helping.

802
01:01:24,097 --> 01:01:27,067
All right, here we go.
For real this time.

803
01:01:36,985 --> 01:01:38,328
I can do this.

804
01:01:57,047 --> 01:01:58,299
Agh! I hate you!

805
01:02:02,135 --> 01:02:03,182
Ah.

806
01:02:58,525 --> 01:02:59,572
Eh.

807
01:03:00,860 --> 01:03:02,407
Kevin?
Mmm?

808
01:03:02,529 --> 01:03:03,781
Tom?

809
01:03:03,863 --> 01:03:04,955
Hello!

810
01:03:05,532 --> 01:03:07,284
Kampai! Kampai!

811
01:03:07,367 --> 01:03:08,584
H U h? Kampai!

812
01:03:20,547 --> 01:03:21,594
Bah!

813
01:03:26,011 --> 01:03:27,012
Oh.

814
01:03:29,014 --> 01:03:32,234
Cinco de May-ya-yo!
Cinco de May-ya-yo!

815
01:03:41,192 --> 01:03:42,193
EDITH: Whoa!

816
01:03:42,319 --> 01:03:44,447
This place is awesome!

817
01:03:47,240 --> 01:03:49,038
Okay. Let's party, huh?

818
01:03:49,117 --> 01:03:51,836
But first,
let's go over the rules.

819
01:03:51,911 --> 01:03:55,165
Because what is fun
without the rules?

820
01:03:55,332 --> 01:03:56,959
Agnes, easy on the churros.

821
01:03:57,250 --> 01:03:59,378
Edith, try not to kill anyone.
Hai!

822
01:03:59,627 --> 01:04:00,674
Margo!

823
01:04:00,754 --> 01:04:01,880
Hello, Mr. Gru.

824
01:04:01,963 --> 01:04:03,340
Okay.

825
01:04:03,923 --> 01:04:04,970
Gru!

826
01:04:05,091 --> 01:04:10,018
There must be the standard 6 feet
of space between you and boys.

827
01:04:10,138 --> 01:04:11,890
Especially this boy.

828
01:04:13,475 --> 01:04:14,977
Ah, you are a funny man.

829
01:04:15,143 --> 01:04:17,942
There are no rules, sefior.
It's Cinco de Mayo.

830
01:04:18,104 --> 01:04:20,323
Come on!
They're starting the dance!

831
01:04:20,440 --> 01:04:21,942
IArriba!

832
01:05:18,790 --> 01:05:23,512
So glad you could
make it, mi compadre.

833
01:05:24,045 --> 01:05:25,422
Hey, what's wrong?

834
01:05:25,505 --> 01:05:27,507
Oh, nothing.
Nothing is wrong.

835
01:05:27,632 --> 01:05:32,354
I'm just chilling with the
guac, from my chip hat.

836
01:05:35,098 --> 01:05:38,648
Gru, please. I know
that look all too well.

837
01:05:38,726 --> 01:05:41,149
It is the look
of a broken heart.

838
01:05:41,229 --> 01:05:42,572
How did you know?

839
01:05:42,689 --> 01:05:46,159
Believe me, my friend,
I too have spent many nights

840
01:05:46,234 --> 01:05:49,909
trying to drown my
sorrows in guacamole.

841
01:05:50,238 --> 01:05:52,332
You?
Yes.

842
01:05:53,032 --> 01:05:56,161
But we are survivors.

843
01:05:56,244 --> 01:06:00,374
There's much more to
us than meets the eye.

844
01:06:00,999 --> 01:06:02,922
Enjoy the party-

845
01:06:56,596 --> 01:06:57,597
Huh.

846
01:07:18,868 --> 01:07:20,711
Ah-ha!

847
01:07:23,831 --> 01:07:25,083
Ouch!

848
01:07:42,016 --> 01:07:43,313
Say what?

849
01:07:56,281 --> 01:07:59,160
Would you like some
peanuts or pretzels?

850
01:08:03,871 --> 01:08:05,748
That's a good joke.

851
01:08:09,877 --> 01:08:12,175
I just did a boom boom.

852
01:08:13,840 --> 01:08:15,968
I really need you to
make a choice, hon.

853
01:08:17,510 --> 01:08:19,012
I choose Gru.

854
01:08:19,804 --> 01:08:21,852
I choose Gru!

855
01:08:25,560 --> 01:08:27,608
Thank you, Gru stewardess!

856
01:08:27,687 --> 01:08:29,360
You're welcome!

857
01:08:47,665 --> 01:08:48,712
Aah!

858
01:09:02,764 --> 01:09:06,394
You have not lost
your touch, my friend.

859
01:09:06,476 --> 01:09:08,774
Ah-ha! I knew it!

860
01:09:08,895 --> 01:09:10,442
You are El Macho!

861
01:09:10,605 --> 01:09:12,824
That's right!

862
01:09:12,899 --> 01:09:14,572
Nobody believed me!

863
01:09:14,651 --> 01:09:16,494
Ho-ho! But I knew
you weren't dead!

864
01:09:17,737 --> 01:09:21,412
Of course not.
I merely faked my death.

865
01:09:22,200 --> 01:09:24,373
But now, it's time for me

866
01:09:24,452 --> 01:09:28,423
to make
a spectacular return to evil.

867
01:09:28,956 --> 01:09:34,338
Doctor, I think it's time we
showed Gru what we're up to here.

868
01:09:34,420 --> 01:09:36,468
Dr. Nefario?

869
01:09:36,547 --> 01:09:38,720
Nice to see you, Gru.

870
01:09:39,384 --> 01:09:40,431
Wha...?

871
01:09:40,510 --> 01:09:43,514
So, this is your
new job opportunity?

872
01:09:43,596 --> 01:09:46,566
Absolutely.
You're gonna like this.

873
01:09:51,604 --> 01:09:52,730
EDUARDO: Sorry.

874
01:09:52,855 --> 01:09:56,610
I had to borrow some of your minions,
but it was for a worthy cause.

875
01:09:57,110 --> 01:09:59,704
Oh! Kevin!

876
01:09:59,779 --> 01:10:02,282
No, he's not Kevin anymore.

877
01:10:02,448 --> 01:10:07,375
Now he is an indestructible,
mindless killing machine!

878
01:10:07,453 --> 01:10:08,454
Bah!

879
01:10:08,621 --> 01:10:10,544
Just watch this.

880
01:10:24,137 --> 01:10:25,184
Bah!

881
01:10:25,263 --> 01:10:27,140
And here's the best part!

882
01:10:27,265 --> 01:10:30,485
I got an army of them!

883
01:10:41,696 --> 01:10:42,822
Bah!

884
01:10:42,947 --> 01:10:47,077
Soon I will unleash
them on the world,

885
01:10:47,201 --> 01:10:51,297
and if anyone,
anyone tries to stop them...

886
01:10:51,372 --> 01:10:52,498
Yeow!

887
01:10:52,582 --> 01:10:55,176
Their city gets eaten!

888
01:10:55,710 --> 01:10:57,212
We can do it together.

889
01:10:57,336 --> 01:10:58,508
Together?

890
01:10:58,629 --> 01:10:59,676
Together!

891
01:11:00,298 --> 01:11:03,051
I have admired your
work for years, amigo.

892
01:11:03,134 --> 01:11:06,513
Stealing the Moon!
Are you kidding?

893
01:11:06,637 --> 01:11:08,935
We would be unstoppable!

894
01:11:09,015 --> 01:11:11,689
Men like you, men like me.

895
01:11:11,768 --> 01:11:15,864
We should be ruling the world!

896
01:11:15,980 --> 01:11:17,698
So, are you in?

897
01:11:18,107 --> 01:11:19,108
Woo-hoo!

898
01:11:19,859 --> 01:11:21,702
Uh, yeah, probably.

899
01:11:22,278 --> 01:11:23,370
Probably?

900
01:11:23,488 --> 01:11:26,116
I mean, yes, yes!
Of course, yes.

901
01:11:26,199 --> 01:11:28,998
I just have a lot
going on right now.

902
01:11:29,076 --> 01:11:31,829
I just need to get
some things off my plate

903
01:11:31,913 --> 01:11:35,213
before we start taking over
the world, that's all.

904
01:11:35,333 --> 01:11:37,210
Excuse me?
No, forget it.

905
01:11:37,335 --> 01:11:40,555
One hundred percent! lam in!

906
01:11:40,713 --> 01:11:43,762
I think...
Do you hear that? I do.

907
01:11:43,883 --> 01:11:47,558
That's Agnes calling
me from on the surface.

908
01:11:50,389 --> 01:11:51,857
Totally in!

909
01:11:53,726 --> 01:11:54,898
You know what?

910
01:11:55,019 --> 01:11:57,568
I am not so
convinced that he is in.

911
01:12:09,367 --> 01:12:11,369
Edith, Agnes, come on! Ooh!

912
01:12:11,452 --> 01:12:12,544
Oops, sorry.

913
01:12:12,620 --> 01:12:14,293
We need to go home now.
Where is Margo?

914
01:12:14,372 --> 01:12:15,999
But I didn't get a turn!

915
01:12:22,672 --> 01:12:23,764
Margo!

916
01:12:23,840 --> 01:12:26,138
Come on. We're leaving...

917
01:12:26,467 --> 01:12:28,014
Hey, what's wrong?

918
01:12:28,094 --> 01:12:29,687
I hate boys.

919
01:12:32,849 --> 01:12:34,897
Yes. They stink.

920
01:12:34,976 --> 01:12:37,195
Uh, sorry. Honey,
we got to go.

921
01:13:00,293 --> 01:13:01,795
Oops! Sorry.

922
01:13:06,132 --> 01:13:07,930
Ya!

923
01:13:13,472 --> 01:13:16,271
Hey! Pollito,
what's the matter?

924
01:13:16,350 --> 01:13:17,476
Oh, hey, Eduardo!

925
01:13:17,560 --> 01:13:19,403
Lucia, I apologize.

926
01:13:19,478 --> 01:13:22,231
Pollito,
he's usually not like this.

927
01:13:22,315 --> 01:13:26,991
The same thing happened the
other day with Gru, and...

928
01:13:28,988 --> 01:13:33,585
Oh, well, speaking of Gru, um, have you seen him?
I really need to talk to him.

929
01:13:33,659 --> 01:13:36,833
Yes. I think he's
somewhere around here.

930
01:13:36,913 --> 01:13:38,756
You two are close, no?

931
01:13:38,873 --> 01:13:40,500
Oh, I don't know.

932
01:13:40,583 --> 01:13:43,928
I mean, "close,"
I wouldn't say we were close.

933
01:13:44,003 --> 01:13:46,005
Why, did he say we were close?
Did he say that'?

934
01:13:46,088 --> 01:13:48,591
It's more what he didn't say.

935
01:13:48,674 --> 01:13:52,019
For instance,
he never mentioned

936
01:13:52,094 --> 01:13:55,223
that you were both working
for the Anti-Villain League!

937
01:13:56,432 --> 01:13:58,105
You're coming with me.

938
01:13:58,184 --> 01:13:59,231
Hey!

939
01:14:00,519 --> 01:14:01,896
Crikey!

940
01:14:07,944 --> 01:14:10,413
So, Eduardo's
actually El Macho?

941
01:14:10,529 --> 01:14:11,746
Cool!

942
01:14:11,822 --> 01:14:13,165
No, it is not cool!

943
01:14:13,240 --> 01:14:15,618
Plus, I pretty much
knew it was him all along,

944
01:14:15,701 --> 01:14:17,703
so if anyone's cool, it's me!

945
01:14:19,705 --> 01:14:20,752
Gru!

946
01:14:20,873 --> 01:14:22,921
Well, Dr. Nefario.

947
01:14:23,042 --> 01:14:25,795
El Macho's onto you. He knows
you're working for the A VL.

948
01:14:25,878 --> 01:14:27,846
And he's got your partner.

949
01:14:28,381 --> 01:14:29,724
Lucy?

950
01:14:29,882 --> 01:14:33,102
That's impossible.
She's on her way to Australia!

951
01:14:33,177 --> 01:14:34,303
EDUARDO: Nefario?

952
01:14:34,387 --> 01:14:35,639
Sorry, gotta 9°-'

953
01:14:37,515 --> 01:14:38,858
He's got Lucy?

954
01:14:39,976 --> 01:14:41,523
Not for long.

955
01:14:41,686 --> 01:14:44,064
Come on, we're
getting her out of there.

956
01:16:12,818 --> 01:16:14,035
What was that?

957
01:16:25,873 --> 01:16:27,170
I don't see anything.

958
01:16:40,846 --> 01:16:42,189
Run!

959
01:16:42,890 --> 01:16:43,891
My unicorn!

960
01:16:44,016 --> 01:16:45,359
MARGO: Agnes, no!

961
01:17:19,385 --> 01:17:21,137
Come on! Hurry!

962
01:17:24,557 --> 01:17:25,809
What's the matter?

963
01:17:31,564 --> 01:17:32,565
Bah!

964
01:17:43,075 --> 01:17:44,122
Ooh lé lé.

965
01:17:46,912 --> 01:17:48,164
Kevin!

966
01:17:50,833 --> 01:17:52,426
Dr. Nefario! You're back!

967
01:17:52,585 --> 01:17:54,258
In the flesh.

968
01:17:55,296 --> 01:17:57,515
Behold, the antidote.

969
01:18:00,926 --> 01:18:04,851
Come on. Let's finally put this
horrible jelly to some good use.

970
01:18:16,150 --> 01:18:17,697
Ah! Ah!

971
01:18:20,112 --> 01:18:22,991
Hey, guys, come on!
Stay focused here.

972
01:18:33,834 --> 01:18:34,881
Huh?

973
01:18:34,960 --> 01:18:36,007
Huh?

974
01:18:40,341 --> 01:18:42,059
Uh...

975
01:18:45,846 --> 01:18:47,814
Uh...

976
01:18:48,307 --> 01:18:49,559
Oh.

977
01:19:00,819 --> 01:19:02,036
Uh,

978
01:19:04,990 --> 01:19:07,539
Curses! Foiled again!

979
01:19:07,701 --> 01:19:10,204
These guys captured me!

980
01:19:42,945 --> 01:19:43,992
Uh...

981
01:19:44,071 --> 01:19:45,368
No?

982
01:19:47,241 --> 01:19:48,288
Bah!

983
01:19:48,867 --> 01:19:49,993
Run!

984
01:19:59,044 --> 01:20:00,466
Up that tree!

985
01:20:01,714 --> 01:20:02,840
Hurry! Hurry!

986
01:21:03,901 --> 01:21:05,699
Hello, Gru!

987
01:21:05,819 --> 01:21:09,119
Hey hey!
Nice work, Dr. Nefario!

988
01:21:09,198 --> 01:21:11,371
I put an antidote in the jelly.

989
01:21:11,992 --> 01:21:15,872
I mean, I'm happy to create an
evil army to destroy the world,

990
01:21:15,954 --> 01:21:18,707
but nobody
messes with my family.

991
01:21:18,832 --> 01:21:20,834
Thank you, Doctor.

992
01:21:20,959 --> 01:21:22,882
Now, let's go get the...

993
01:21:24,129 --> 01:21:25,301
Hi!

994
01:21:25,381 --> 01:21:26,758
You brought the girls?

995
01:21:26,840 --> 01:21:28,183
Yes!

996
01:21:28,467 --> 01:21:29,514
Oh.

997
01:21:29,635 --> 01:21:31,057
Was that wrong?

998
01:21:41,146 --> 01:21:43,615
What's happening to my minions?

999
01:21:43,690 --> 01:21:44,782
Gru?

1000
01:21:46,902 --> 01:21:49,576
You guys, take care of
the rest of the minions.

1001
01:21:49,655 --> 01:21:51,657
I'm going to find Lucy.

1002
01:22:01,875 --> 01:22:04,594
Eat jelly, you purple freaks!

1003
01:22:04,670 --> 01:22:06,513
Whoa! Whoa!

1004
01:22:33,907 --> 01:22:35,659
It's over, El Macho.

1005
01:22:35,784 --> 01:22:37,081
Now, where is Lucy?

1006
01:22:38,454 --> 01:22:39,751
Let me show you.

1007
01:22:52,384 --> 01:22:53,852
Oh, hey, Gru!

1008
01:22:53,927 --> 01:22:57,431
Turns out you were right about
the whole El Macho thing, huh?

1009
01:22:57,556 --> 01:22:58,899
Yay!

1010
01:22:59,475 --> 01:23:02,979
One push of this button,
and I send that rocket

1011
01:23:03,061 --> 01:23:07,441
straight into the same volcano
where I faked my death.

1012
01:23:07,566 --> 01:23:10,490
Only this time, it's for real.

1013
01:23:10,569 --> 01:23:12,037
No!

1014
01:23:12,112 --> 01:23:13,580
Yah!

1015
01:23:13,697 --> 01:23:15,119
Tallyho!

1016
01:23:21,955 --> 01:23:25,585
We could have ruled
the world together, Gru!

1017
01:23:26,168 --> 01:23:27,545
But now,

1018
01:23:27,920 --> 01:23:29,593
you're gonna die.

1019
01:23:53,779 --> 01:23:55,656
On!

1020
01:24:14,967 --> 01:24:15,968
Ah!

1021
01:24:42,411 --> 01:24:44,755
Mmm, lipstick taser!

1022
01:24:44,871 --> 01:24:47,090
Aw, he copied me.

1023
01:24:53,338 --> 01:24:57,684
I am not afraid
of yourjelly guns.

1024
01:24:57,801 --> 01:25:01,101
Oh, this ain't
ajelly gun, sunshine.

1025
01:25:09,521 --> 01:25:10,568
Ho-oh!

1026
01:25:15,235 --> 01:25:17,329
Don't worry about me,
Gru, I'll be fine.

1027
01:25:17,404 --> 01:25:19,873
I have survived
lots worse than this.

1028
01:25:19,948 --> 01:25:21,370
Okay, that's not entirely true.

1029
01:25:21,450 --> 01:25:23,498
I'm actually kind of
freaking out up here!

1030
01:25:23,577 --> 01:25:25,671
Don't worry,
I will get you out of this.

1031
01:25:34,212 --> 01:25:36,385
I really hate that chicken.

1032
01:26:01,281 --> 01:26:03,375
LUCY: ls there a red one?
It's usually the red one!

1033
01:26:06,119 --> 01:26:08,747
Gru, anytime now!

1034
01:26:10,499 --> 01:26:13,218
Listen, Lucy, we may not
get out of this alive,

1035
01:26:13,293 --> 01:26:15,637
so I need to
ask you a question.

1036
01:26:15,712 --> 01:26:16,713
Uh, better make it quick.

1037
01:26:17,255 --> 01:26:20,634
If I had asked you out on a
date, what would you have said?

1038
01:26:21,093 --> 01:26:22,345
Are you kidding me?

1039
01:26:22,427 --> 01:26:23,474
Yes!

1040
01:26:25,472 --> 01:26:26,894
Jump!

1041
01:26:39,528 --> 01:26:40,996
Lucy!

1042
01:26:41,655 --> 01:26:43,908
Lucy, where are you?

1043
01:26:47,119 --> 01:26:48,336
Oh, Lucy!

1044
01:26:49,121 --> 01:26:50,293
Gru!

1045
01:26:54,292 --> 01:26:58,092
Sorry! I guess you need your
arms to tread water, huh?

1046
01:27:06,638 --> 01:27:08,311
They'll be back.

1047
01:27:38,712 --> 01:27:41,511
Underwear...

1048
01:27:49,931 --> 01:27:52,684
ALL: Underwear...

1049
01:28:01,276 --> 01:28:04,120
Underwear...

1050
01:28:13,538 --> 01:28:14,585
Oh!

1051
01:28:19,711 --> 01:28:22,965
Can I be
the first to say, "Ew!"

1052
01:28:24,049 --> 01:28:26,552
Underwear...

1053
01:28:42,192 --> 01:28:43,284
Okay.

1054
01:28:44,444 --> 01:28:45,661
Excuse me.

1055
01:28:47,572 --> 01:28:49,449
Um, hi, excuse me.

1056
01:28:57,332 --> 01:28:58,424
Uh,

1057
01:28:58,708 --> 01:29:02,463
hi, everybody.
I'd like to make some toast.

1058
01:29:02,587 --> 01:29:03,759
Uh...

1059
01:29:04,798 --> 01:29:06,220
Okay.

1060
01:29:07,509 --> 01:29:08,726
She, um...

1061
01:29:08,802 --> 01:29:13,057
She kisses my boo-boos,
she braids my hair.

1062
01:29:13,181 --> 01:29:16,025
We love you,
mothers, everywhere.

1063
01:29:16,643 --> 01:29:19,863
And my new mom,
Lucy, is beyond compare.

1064
01:29:19,938 --> 01:29:21,281
MINIONS: Avvvv.

1065
01:29:21,398 --> 01:29:22,399
Aw.

1066
01:29:29,447 --> 01:29:31,700
To the bride and Gru!

1067
01:29:52,220 --> 01:29:53,267
Yeah!

1068
01:30:04,941 --> 01:30:07,444
LUCY: Woo-hool
I'm so happy!

1069
01:30:17,537 --> 01:30:18,584
Huh? Ha!

1070
01:30:31,009 --> 01:30:32,010
Bah!

1071
01:30:53,031 --> 01:30:54,954
Hey, Bob! Stuart!

1072
01:31:27,148 --> 01:31:28,320
Eh!

1073
01:31:28,900 --> 01:31:29,947
No?

1074
01:31:31,861 --> 01:31:32,908
Ah!

1075
01:31:36,074 --> 01:31:37,166
Bob!

1076
01:31:44,958 --> 01:31:46,005
Uh-oh!

1077
01:32:00,223 --> 01:32:02,146
Okay.

1078
01:32:30,378 --> 01:32:31,425
Okay.

1079
01:32:49,230 --> 01:32:50,277
Aah!

1080
01:33:39,906 --> 01:33:41,658
Shh!

1081
01:33:51,626 --> 01:33:53,128
Blah.